<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google Trends on Kaka&#39;s Note</title>
    <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/tags/google-trends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google Trends on Kaka&#39;s Note</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://kaka-lin.github.io/tags/google-trends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/000_template/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/000_template/</guid>
      <description>0. Template Discription Example:  Solution:  Runtime: ms (%) Memory Usage: MB (%)   Time complexity Space complexity </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>LeetCode https://github.com/kaka-lin/Notes/blob/master/DSA/leetcode/python/000_template.md
   # Title Solution Topics Difficulty     1 Tow Sum Python Array, Hash Table Easy   2 Add Tow Numbers Python Linked List, Math Medium   7 Reverse Integer Python  Easy   9 Palindrome Number Python  Easy   13 Roman to Integer Python Math, String Easy   19 Remove Nth Node From End of List Python Linked List, Two Pointers Medium   21 Merge Two Sorted Lists Python Linked List Easy   24 Swap Nodes in Pairs Python Linked List Medium   27 Remove Element Python Array, Two Pointers Easy   28 Implement strStr() Python String, Two Pointers Easy   35 Search Insert Position Python Array, Binary Search Easy   53 Maximum Subarray Python Dynamic Programming Easy   70 Climbing Stairs Python Dynamic Programming Easy   83 Remove Duplicates from Sorted List Python Linked List Easy   94 Binary Tree Inorder Traversal Python Tree Medium   98 Validate Binary Search Tree Python Binary Search Tree Medium   100 Same Tree Python Tree Easy   102 Binary Tree Level Order Traversal Python Tree, Breadth-first Search Medium   118 Pascal&amp;rsquo;s Triangle Python Array, Recursion, Dynamic Programming Easy   119 Pascal&amp;rsquo;s Triangle II Python Array, Recursion, Dynamic Programming Easy   136 Single Number Python List, Hash Table, Bit Manipulation Easy   144 Binary Tree Preorder Traversal Python Stack, Tree Medium   145 Binary Tree Postorder Traversal Python Stack, Tree Hard   160 Intersection of Two Linked Lists Python Linked List Easy   167 Two Sum II - Input array is sorted Python Array, Two Pointers, Binary Search Easy   169 Majority Element Python Array, Divide and Conquer, Bit Manipulation Easy   191 Number of 1 Bits Python Bit Manipulation Easy   202 Happy Number Python Hash Table, Math Easy   203 Remove Linked List Elements Python Linked List Easy   206 Reverse Linked List Python Linked List Easy   217 Contains Duplicate Python Array, Hash Table Easy   226 Invert Binary Tree Python Tree Easy   234 Palindrome Linked List Python Linked List, Two Pointers Easy   236 Lowest Common Ancestor of a Binary Tree Python Tree, Stack, Recursion Medium   240 Search a 2D Matrix II Python Binary Search, Divide and Conquer Medium   242 Valid Anagram Python Hash Table Easy   297 Serialize and Deserialize Binary Tree Python Tree, Stack, Recursion Hard   344 344.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>Data Structure and Algorithms (DSA)  Recursion Dynamic Programming  LeetCode  LeetCode  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>Bitonic Champion Problem   Input: A bitonic sequence A[1], A[2], &amp;hellip;, A[n] for distinct positive integers.
  Output: the index $i$ with $1 {\leq} i {\leq} n$ such that
$$A[i] = \max_{1 {\leq} j {\leq} n} A[j]$$
  Bitonic sequence The bitonic sequence means &amp;quot;increasing&amp;quot; before the champion and &amp;quot;decreasing&amp;quot; after the champion  Exmaple
3 7 9 17 35 28 21 18 6 4  Bitonic Champion Problem Complexity   Upper bound: $O(logn)$</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>Maximum Subarray Problem   Input: A sequence A[1], A[2], &amp;hellip;, A[n] of integers.
  Output: Two indicex $i$ and $j$ with $1 {\leq} i {\leq} j {\leq} n$ that maximize
$$A[i] + A[i+1] + \cdots + A[j]$$
  Solution 1. Divide and Conquer  Base case (n = 1)  Return itself (maximum subarray)   Recursive case (n &amp;gt; 1)  Divide the array into two sub-arrays Find the maximum sub-array recuresively Merge the result    Bitonic Champion Problem Complexity   Upper bound: $O(n)$</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>Merge Sort One of the classic examples of the divide-and-conquer algorithm is the merge sort algorithm. Merge sort is an efficient and general-purpose sorting algorithm. Intuition There are two apporaches to implement the merge sort algorithm: top-down or bottom-up. The merge sort algorithm can be divided into three steps, like all divide-and-conquer algorithms. 1. Divide the given unsorted list into several sublists. (Divide) 2. Sort each of the sublists recursively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>Quick Sort Quick sort is another classical divide-and-conquer algorithm for sorting. Intuition The quick sort algorithm can be implemented in three steps, namely dividing the problem, solving the subproblems and combing the results of subproblems. In detail, given a list of values to sort, the quick sort algorithm works in following steps: First, it selects a value from the list, which serves as a pivot value to divide the list</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>Divide and Conquer Solve a problwm recursively
Three steps   Divide
Divide the problem into a number of subproblems that are smaller instances of the same problem.    Conquer
Conquer the subproblems by solving them recursively.    Base case (Termination condition): Solve the subproblems if the subproblem sizes are small enough.
  Recursive case: Recursively solve itself.
    Combine
Combine the solutions to the subproblems into the solution for the original problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>Tower of Hanoi  Problem: move n disks from A to C Rules:  Move one disk at a time. Cannot place a large dosk onto a smaller disk.    Reference  ADA, NTU CSIE  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>Recursion </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>Python Environment Setup Tutorials Medium: Install Python on Windows
 Windows macOS Ubuntu  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>Python Tutorial  Installing Python  Table of Contents   01. Python Basics
  02. Flow Control
  03. List
  04. Dictionary
  05. Function
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaka-lin.github.io/1/01/readme/</guid>
      <description>My Learning Notes My Medium: AIoT Taipei
  Python
  Data Structure and Algorithms (DSA)
  Database
  DevOps
  Data Science
  Scripts   Convert ipynb to md
# all `ipynb` files $ python convert_ipynb_to_md.py # the specific `ipynb` file python convert_ipynb_to_md.py --ipynb_file {specific ipynb file}    Adding Front Matter to Markdown file
# all `md` files except `REAMDE.md` $ python3 add_front_matter_to_md.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
